<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<anime>
  <entry>
    <id>356</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night</title>
    <english>Fate/stay night</english>
    <synonyms>Fate - Stay Night</synonyms>
    <episodes>24</episodes>
    <score>7.60</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2006-01-07</start_date>
    <end_date>2006-06-17</end_date>
    <synopsis>After a mysterious inferno kills his family, Shirou is saved and adopted by Kiritsugu Emiya, who teaches him the ways of magic and justice.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
One night, years after Kiritsugu&amp;#039;s death, Shirou is cleaning at school, when he finds himself caught in the middle of a deadly encounter between two superhumans known as Servants. During his attempt to escape, the boy is caught by one of the Servants and receives a life-threatening injury. Miraculously, he survives, but the same Servant returns to finish what he started. In desperation, Shirou summons a Servant of his own, a knight named Saber. The two must now participate in the Fifth Holy Grail War, a battle royale of seven Servants and the mages who summoned them, with the grand prize being none other than the omnipotent Holy Grail itself.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[i]Fate/stay night[/i] follows Shirou as he struggles to find the fine line between a hero and a killer, his ideals clashing with the harsh reality around him. Will the boy become a hero like his foster father, or die trying?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/30327.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>394</id>
    <title>Ai Yori Aoshi: Enishi</title>
    <english>Ai Yori Aoshi: Enishi</english>
    <synonyms>Bluer Than Indigo: Fate</synonyms>
    <episodes>12</episodes>
    <score>7.27</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-10-13</start_date>
    <end_date>2003-12-29</end_date>
    <synopsis>Two years after meeting Aoi, Kaoru and gang are still up to their normal habits. Kaoru now in grad school and the tenants being as rowdy as ever what will become of Aoi and Kaoru's love.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Two years has passed since Aoi and Kaoru were freed from the bonds of their families. They continue to live their normal lives with their usual friends in their house.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/10/71425.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1474</id>
    <title>City Hunter: Ai to Shukumei no Magnum</title>
    <english>City Hunter: .357 Magnum</english>
    <synonyms>City Hunter: A Magnum of Love's Destination; City Hunter: Magnum of Love and Destiny; City Hunter: Magnum of Love and Fate</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.59</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>1989-06-17</start_date>
    <end_date>1989-06-17</end_date>
    <synopsis>A beautiful pianist comes to Tokyo for a charity concert, and City Hunter is there. But music isn`t his forte; he wants lessons in the language of love. Desperation becomes the word of the day as the bodies start dropping. A foreign dignitary is assassinated in cold blood. Secret agents scour the streets for a missing microchip. Diplomatic infighting swirls around the upcoming concert, and City Hunter is the only hope! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: AnimeNfo)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/6/3023.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6922</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night Movie: Unlimited Blade Works</title>
    <english>Fate/stay night - Unlimited Blade Works</english>
    <synonyms>Gekijouban Fate/Stay Night: Unlimited Blade Works; Fate/stay night Movie; Fate/stay night UBW</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.60</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2010-01-23</start_date>
    <end_date>2010-01-23</end_date>
    <synopsis>This is the adaptation of the second route of the popular visual novel: [i]Fate/stay night[/i]. In this route, Rin Toosaka will be the major female character. Revelations about Shirou and his destiny will be made.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: AnimeNfo)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/9/80350.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>7559</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night TV Reproduction</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fate/stay night Recap; Fate/stay night OVA</synonyms>
    <episodes>2</episodes>
    <score>7.03</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2010-01-17</start_date>
    <end_date>2010-01-17</end_date>
    <synopsis>An edited and condensed version of the TV series.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/7/33537.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>10087</id>
    <title>Fate/Zero</title>
    <english>Fate/Zero</english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>13</episodes>
    <score>8.54</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-10-02</start_date>
    <end_date>2011-12-25</end_date>
    <synopsis>With the promise of granting any wish, the omnipotent Holy Grail triggered three wars in the past, each too cruel and fierce to leave a victor. In spite of that, the wealthy Einzbern family is confident that the Fourth Holy Grail War will be different; namely, with a vessel of the Holy Grail now in their grasp. Solely for this reason, the much hated &amp;quot;Magus Killer&amp;quot; Kiritsugu Emiya is hired by the Einzberns, with marriage to their only daughter Irisviel as binding contract.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Kiritsugu now stands at the center of a cutthroat game of survival, facing off against six other participants, each armed with an ancient familiar, and fueled by unique desires and ideals. Accompanied by his own familiar, Saber, the notorious mercenary soon finds his greatest opponent in Kirei Kotomine, a priest who seeks salvation from the emptiness within himself in pursuit of Kiritsugu.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Based on the light novel written by Gen Urobuchi, [i]Fate/Zero[/i] depicts the events of the Fourth Holy Grail War&amp;mdash;10 years prior to [i]Fate/stay night[/i]. Witness a battle royale in which no one is guaranteed to survive.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/73249.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>11741</id>
    <title>Fate/Zero 2nd Season</title>
    <english>Fate/Zero 2nd Season</english>
    <synonyms>Fate/Zero Second Season</synonyms>
    <episodes>12</episodes>
    <score>8.75</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-04-08</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-06-24</end_date>
    <synopsis>As the Fourth Holy Grail War rages on with no clear victor in sight, the remaining Servants and their Masters are called upon by Church supervisor Risei Kotomine, in order to band together and confront an impending threat that could unravel the Grail War and bring about the destruction of Fuyuki City. The uneasy truce soon collapses as Masters demonstrate that they will do anything in their power, no matter how despicable, to win.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Seeds of doubt are sown between Kiritsugu Emiya and Saber, his Servant, as their conflicting ideologies on heroism and chivalry clash. Meanwhile, an ominous bond forms between Kirei Kotomine, who still seeks to find his purpose in life, and one of the remaining Servants. As the countdown to the end of the war reaches zero, the cost of winning begins to blur the line between victory and defeat.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/8/41125.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>12565</id>
    <title>Fate/Prototype</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.03</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2011-12-31</start_date>
    <end_date>2011-12-31</end_date>
    <synopsis>[i]Fate/Prototype[/i] is a digest version of Kinoko Nasu&amp;#039;s original version of [i]Fate/stay night[/i].</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/51045.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>13183</id>
    <title>Fate/Zero Remix</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fate/Zero Remix I; Fate/Zero Remix II</synonyms>
    <episodes>2</episodes>
    <score>7.27</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-03-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-04-01</end_date>
    <synopsis>Two recap specials titled &quot;Fate/Zero Remix I&quot; and &quot;Fate/Zero Remix II&quot; serve to summarize the first 13 episodes of Fate/Zero.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/6/37081.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>13263</id>
    <title>Fate/Zero: Onegai! Einzbern Soudanshitsu</title>
    <english>Fate/Zero: Please! Einzbern Counseling Room</english>
    <synonyms>Fate/Zero Specials; Please! Einzbern Consultation Room</synonyms>
    <episodes>6</episodes>
    <score>6.78</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2012-03-07</start_date>
    <end_date>2012-09-19</end_date>
    <synopsis>Written by Kinoko Nasu, these specials are included in the BD box sets I &amp;amp; II.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Join Irisviel as she helps Disciple No. Zero understand more details and history relating to the Holy Grail War.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/64273.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>14829</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya</title>
    <english>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya</english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya</synonyms>
    <episodes>10</episodes>
    <score>7.28</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-06-22</start_date>
    <end_date>2013-09-07</end_date>
    <synopsis>Illyasviel von Einzbern is a normal schoolgirl in Japan. She lives with her overachieving nice guy older brother Shirou Emiya and her two maids, her parents are perpetually out of the country, and she has fanciful dreams of using magic to make her dreams of love with Shirou come true. Enter fierce rivals Rin Tohsaka and Luviagelita Edelfelt, two Magi who have been sent to Japan by Zelretch the Wizard Marshall, Master of Parallel Worlds, with the powerful sentient Kaleidosticks to collect the mysterious Class Cards and clean up their mess. After getting fed up with their constant infighting, one Kaleidostick, Magical Ruby, senses Illya&amp;#039;s fleeting dream of magic and leaves Rin for her, tricking her into becoming a magical girl. Now Illya is being forced by Rin to collect the dangerous Class Cards in her place. But perhaps more dangerous still are Illya&amp;#039;s own mysteries that may have unknowingly attracted Ruby to her.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/7/52603.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>18851</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya: Undoukai de Dance!</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya OVA</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.79</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-03-10</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-03-10</end_date>
    <synopsis>Tatsuko of class 5-1 is really excited about the upcoming school sports festival, her proposal for a new &amp;quot;Eel Scooping&amp;quot; event is less than enthusiastically received though, especially by Suzuka. Illya mentions the main event dance to Miyu, and as teacher Taiga Fujimura points out, it entails a huge reward, but will require quite a bit of practice.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And so the close friends: sarcastic Nanaki, level-headed Suzuka, excitable Tatsuko, energetic Illya, shy Mimi, and reserved but athletic Miyu are off to win the dance event for the honour of their class and for Fujimura, who seems to have some saucy bet going on that she most definitely needs to win, or so the girls misunderstand.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: AniDB) </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/7/60279.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>19109</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya Specials</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya Specials</synonyms>
    <episodes>5</episodes>
    <score>6.86</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-09-27</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-01-31</end_date>
    <synopsis>Specials bundled with the all the BD/DVD volumes.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/51235.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>19165</id>
    <title>Fate/Zero Cafe</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fate/Zero Café</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.41</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-07-13</start_date>
    <end_date>2013-07-13</end_date>
    <synopsis>The story re-imagines the cast of the [i]Fate/Zero[/i] as cute super-deformed characters who open a caf&amp;eacute;, led by Saber as the manager.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/7/51943.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>19337</id>
    <title>Momoya x Peeping Life: Go en Desu yo!</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Peeping Life: This Is Fate!</synonyms>
    <episodes>4</episodes>
    <score>5.67</score>
    <type>ONA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-04-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2013-05-16</end_date>
    <synopsis>This is a sketch drama consisting of four episodes on dating in collaboration with the leading food company Momoya.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/6/52087.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>20509</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei!</title>
    <english>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei!</english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 2wei!; Prisma☆Illya 2nd Season</synonyms>
    <episodes>10</episodes>
    <score>7.47</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-07-10</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-09-11</end_date>
    <synopsis>The magical girls are back, and ready for another round of adventure! After successfully recovering the Class Cards, fifth graders-turned magical girls Illya and Miyu think they can finally take it easy. But as fate would have it, the girls are once again called back into active duty when they find out that the Cards have left some very nasty side effects on their world. However, their seemingly easy mission goes totally awry with the appearance of a dark stranger who looks just like Illya! Who is this new but familiar face, where did she come from, and what does she want from Illya? With the arrival of this new foe, it seems like Illya&amp;#039;s finally met her match when her everyday life takes one dark turn!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Crunchyroll)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/12/64175.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>20543</id>
    <title>Bayonetta: Bloody Fate</title>
    <english>Bayonetta: Bloody Fate</english>
    <synonyms>BAYONETTA BLOODYFATE</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>6.80</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-11-23</start_date>
    <end_date>2013-11-23</end_date>
    <synopsis>Driven to recover her memories after waking in a coffin at the bottom of a lake 20 years ago, Bayonetta hunts down the forces of Heaven day and night in search of clues to her forgotten past, and to uphold her pact with the demonic forces she draws her powers from as an Umbra Witch. She is armed and guided by the mysterious bartender and weapon-smith, Rodin, and following her every footstep is the intrepid journalist, Luka Redgrave, who believes that she has something to do with the death of his father and will stop at nothing to get the truth. Her quest takes a promising turn when she encounters a little girl named Cereza, but standing in her way is a rival Umbra Witch named Jeanne, who works for the very forces that she should be opposing.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[i]Bayonetta: Bloody Fate[/i] is an action-packed anime film that explores the connection between all of characters and works to unravel just how they are seemingly entwined in a conspiracy that eclipses them all.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/55441.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>22297</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night: Unlimited Blade Works</title>
    <english>Fate/stay night [Unlimited Blade Works]</english>
    <synonyms>Fate/stay night (2014); Fate - Stay Night</synonyms>
    <episodes>12</episodes>
    <score>8.46</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-10-12</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-12-28</end_date>
    <synopsis>The Holy Grail War is a battle royale among seven magi who serve as Masters. Masters, through the use of the command seals they are given when they enter the war, command Heroic Spirits known as Servants to fight for them in battle. In the Fifth Holy Grail War, Rin Toosaka is among the magi entering the competition. With her Servant, Archer, she hopes to obtain the ultimate prize&amp;mdash;the Holy Grail, a magical artifact capable of granting its wielder any wish.&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
One of Rin&amp;#039;s classmates, Emiya Shirou, accidentally enters the competition and ends up commanding a Servant of his own known as Saber. As they find themselves facing mutual enemies, Rin and Shirou decide to form a temporary alliance as they challenge their opponents in the Holy Grail War. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/12/67333.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>22671</id>
    <title>Momoya x Peeping Life: Go en Desu yo! II</title>
    <english>Peeping Life: This Is Fate! II</english>
    <synonyms>Momoya x Peeping Life: Go en Desu yo! 2; Peeping Life: Go en Desu yo! Season II - Okawari -; Peeping Life: Go en Desu yo! Season 2 - Okawari -</synonyms>
    <episodes>5</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>ONA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2013-12-19</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-01-16</end_date>
    <synopsis>A continuation of last season as Shiromeshi-kun continues his attempts at dating and finding refuge in Momoya food toppings.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/59025.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>25011</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei! Specials</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 2wei!: First Bra - Illya-hen; Prisma☆Illya 2nd Season: First Bra - Illya-hen; Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei!: First Bra - Illya-hen</synonyms>
    <episodes>5</episodes>
    <score>6.91</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-09-26</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-01-30</end_date>
    <synopsis>Short specials included with the Blu-ray/DVD releases of the TV series.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/11/64197.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>25537</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night Movie: Heaven's Feel</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>2017-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>2017-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Emiya Shirou is a young magus who attends Homurahara Academy in Fuyuki City. One day after cleaning the Archery Dojo in his school, he catches a glimpse of a fight between superhuman beings, and he gets involved in the Holy Grail War, a ritual where magi called Masters fight each other with their Servants to win the Holy Grail. Shirou joins the battle to stop an evildoer from winning the Grail and to save innocent people, but everything goes wrong when a mysterious &amp;quot;Shadow&amp;quot; begins to indiscriminately kill people in Fuyuki...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/10/79303.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>26057</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei! OVA</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 2wei! OVA</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.16</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-07-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-07-25</end_date>
    <synopsis>Based on the manga by the same name by Hiroyama Hiroshi, itself a spin-off of the [i]Fate/stay night[/i] erotic visual novel by Type-Moon.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Note: Bundled with the limited edition of the sixth [i]Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma Illya 3rei!![/i] magical girl manga volume.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: AniDB)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/76646.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>27525</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei Herz!</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 2wei! Herz</synonyms>
    <episodes>10</episodes>
    <score>7.37</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-07-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-09-26</end_date>
    <synopsis>Based on the [i]Fate/Kaleid Liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei![/i] manga by Hiroshi Hiroyama, which is a spin-off of the [i]Fate/stay night[/i] erotic visual novel by Type-Moon.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/7/75297.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>27821</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night: Unlimited Blade Works - Prologue</title>
    <english>Fate/stay night: Unlimited Blade Works - Prologue</english>
    <synonyms>Fate/stay night (2014) Episode 00</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.37</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2014-10-05</start_date>
    <end_date>2014-10-05</end_date>
    <synopsis>Fuyuki City&amp;mdash;a city surrounded by the ocean and the mountains becomes the setting for an age-old ritual. To realize the mythical Holy Grail, which is said to grant any wish from its possessor, seven masters are given seven heroic spirits chosen by the Grail. These heroic spirits or servants are: Saber, Lancer, Archer, Rider, Caster, Assassin, Berserker.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Each master will enter into a contract with their assigned servants and battle the other masters and servants to the death until only one pair remains...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This is the &amp;quot;Holy Grail War.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This story focuses primarily on the heroine Rin Toosaka. After her father&amp;#039;s death, Rin enters the Holy Grail War as the sole heir to the prestigious Toosaka Household, with her servant Archer. But, she soon finds out that Shirou Emiya, a boy from her high school has gotten himself involved in the battles and unexpectedly saves him when he is fatally injured.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Aniplex USA)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/9/67425.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>28701</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night: Unlimited Blade Works 2nd Season</title>
    <english>Fate/stay night [Unlimited Blade Works] (2015)</english>
    <synonyms>Fate/stay night (2015); Fate - Stay Night</synonyms>
    <episodes>13</episodes>
    <score>8.47</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-04-05</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-06-28</end_date>
    <synopsis>Fuyuki City will be changed forever following the events that will come to be known as the Fifth Holy Grail War. With the Masters and Servants slowly revealing themselves and their intentions, the stage is set for the grand finale, and at the center of it all is Shirou Emiya and Rin Toosaka.&lt;br /&gt;
The Holy Grail War continues, with each Master and Servant duo making their move for the omnipotent wish granter. Caster&amp;rsquo;s plans have been set in motion, beginning with taking Saber captive while Rin and Archer go their separate ways to continue their fights on their own. Without Saber&amp;rsquo;s aid, Shirou&amp;rsquo;s principles are put to the ultimate test. With many battles to come with expected and unexpected enemies, Shirou&amp;rsquo;s resolve begins to take form. Is his desire to protect people and become a hero, genuine? Or are they simply borrowed feelings? And will it be enough to carry him to the end?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Aniplex USA) &lt;br /&gt;
</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/11/72863.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>31056</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei Herz! Specials</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 2wei Herz!: Beast, Futatabi!</synonyms>
    <episodes>5</episodes>
    <score>7.03</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-09-25</start_date>
    <end_date>2016-01-29</end_date>
    <synopsis>The official website of the [i]Fate/kaleid liner Prisma Illya[/i] anime franchise revealed on Friday that the Blu-ray Disc volumes and the limited-edition DVD volumes of the [i]Fate/kaleid liner Prisma Illya 2wei Herz![/i] anime will each contain a five-minute episode of a short anime titled &amp;quot;Beast, Again!&amp;quot; (Beast, Futatabi!).&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: ANN)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/77429.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>31389</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night: Unlimited Blade Works 2nd Season - Sunny Day</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.42</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2015-10-07</start_date>
    <end_date>2015-10-07</end_date>
    <synopsis>Included with the second Blu-ray box set for the series, the short adapts &amp;quot;sunny day,&amp;quot; an alternate &amp;quot;good&amp;quot; ending to the &amp;quot;Unlimited Blade Works&amp;quot; route from the original Fate/stay night game. </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/75684.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>31706</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 3rei!!</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 3rei!!</synonyms>
    <episodes>0</episodes>
    <score>8.21</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>2016-07-07</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Fourth season of the [i]Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya[/i] series.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/79946.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33047</id>
    <title>Fate/Extra Last Encore</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>0</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>2017-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Waking up in a strange virtual world with no recollection of the past, Hakuno finds himself forced to fight for survival in a war he does not understand for a prize beyond value; the opportunity to have one&amp;#039;s wish granted. With only an enigmatic &amp;quot;Servant&amp;quot; by his side, Hakuno Kishinami will have to face both friends and foes in battles to the death in order to not only gain possession of a mysterious object known as the &amp;quot;Holy Grail,&amp;quot; but also to find the answer to the most important question of all: &amp;quot;Who am I?&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
(Source: Type-Moon Wikia)</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/8/79299.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33049</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night Movie: Heaven's Feel 2</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>0000-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Second of three movies adapting the third route of Fate/stay night. </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/79291.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33050</id>
    <title>Fate/stay night Movie: Heaven's Feel 3</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms></synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>Movie</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>0000-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Final of three movies in an adaption of the third route of Fate/stay night.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/79292.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>33456</id>
    <title>Fate/kaleid liner Prisma☆Illya 3rei!! Specials</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Prisma Illya 3rei!! Specials</synonyms>
    <episodes>6</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Not yet aired</status>
    <start_date>0000-00-00</start_date>
    <end_date>0000-00-00</end_date>
    <synopsis>Specials included with the Blu-ray Disc/DVD releases. </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/8/80452.jpg</image>
  </entry>
</anime>
